

LYNN TSAI

Graphic & Web Designer Motion Graphics Animator Illustrator



CONTACT



Website

https://tsaichialin.com/portfolio



Email

chialin.tsai@gmail.com



Phone 0918477326



Linkedin

https://linkedin.com/in/tsaichialin

SKILLS

Graphic & Print Design

- · Photoshop · Illustrator
- InDesign

Website

- Figma Adobe XD
- HTML CSS SCSS RWD Git
- · Google Web Designer
- WordPress

Motion Graphics

• After Effects • Lottie

Video Shooting & Editing

- Premiere
- Audition

EDUCATION

MA in Multimedia and Animation Art

National Taiwan University of Arts 2000-2003

BA in Arts and Education

National Taipei University of Education 1995-1999

PROFILE

Lynn Tsai (Chia-lin Tsai), self-driven design professional with 17 years of experience. Enthusiastic designer with problem solving skills. Solid understanding of branding, typography, print and motion graphics. Created and designed eye-catching visual content, such as book, flyer, brochure, website, animation, banner, video, and social media post.

I'm working for a global Fintech company, collaborated with marketing and design team, able to adapt to a fast-paced multinational environment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digital Designer

ZeroLogix 2021 - Present

Zerologix is a Fintech company from Austratralia, my duties included:

- Crafted 100+ video assets for our YouTube channel and Instagram.
- Created print materials, such as posters, flyers, and brochures. Promotional materials, such as social media posts, banner ads, exhibition design.
- Designed company letterhead, presentation template, used regularly by 50+ people within company.

Web Designer

BFM 2019 - 2021

In the advertising agency, my duties included:

- Create website layout and user interface using HTML/CSS/JS, troubleshooting issues across desktop and mobile devices.
- Promotional materials for printed, Google Display Network, banner ads.
- Create custom websites using WordPress.
- Create graphics and animations for YouTube, Facebook videos.

Art Director

A Blissful Moment 2018 - 2019

- Present concepts and design guidelines to animation team, leading projects from concept through to completion.
- Collaborated with concept designers and animators, ensuring that all requirments to meet director needs.

Concept Designer

Gamania Digital Entertainment 2005 - 2017

- · Tell stories through animation, motion graphics, and video editing.
- · Create graphics and animations for TV series and short films.
- · Website content / social media management.

Graphic Designer

XFUNS Creative Magazine 2003 - 2004

Create magazine layout designs and promotional materials.



LYNN TSAI

視覺與網頁設計 動態設計 插畫



CONTACT



Website

https://tsaichialin.com/portfolio



Email

chialin.tsai@gmail.com



Phone 0918477326



Linkedin

https://linkedin.com/in/tsaichialin

SKILLS

圖像設計與印刷

- · Photoshop · Illustrator
- InDesign

網站視覺設計與撰寫

- · Figma · Adobe XD
- HTML CSS SCSS RWD Git
- · Google Web Designer
- WordPress

動態影像與動畫製作

· After Effects · Lottie

影片拍攝剪輯

- Premiere
- Audition

EDUCATION

多媒體動畫藝術研究所 碩士 國立台灣藝術大學 2000-2003

美勞教育學系學士 國立台北教育大學 1995-1999

PROFILE

Lynn Tsai (蔡佳琳),17 年工作經驗的資深設計師,其中有 3 年擔任專案管理職。

對視覺十分敏銳,從品牌視覺、印刷排版、網路廣告、動態影像到影片製作都有豐富經驗。 有解決問題的能力,能獨立執行完成書籍、網站、插畫、動畫、廣告Banner、影片拍攝剪輯 等各項工作。

11年的原創動畫經驗培養出扎實的美術底子。在廣告代理商工作2年,期間與行銷團隊與數據分析師密切合作,產生切合市場需求的內容。目前在澳洲金融科技公司工作1年,與跨國行銷、設計團隊協同工作,能適應跨時區、快節奏的環境。

WORK EXPERIENCE

數位設計

ZeroLogix 2021 - Present

Zerologix 是一間來自澳洲的金融科技公司,我的工作包括:

- · 拍攝與剪輯超過100支金融知識影片,提供 YouTube 公司頻道與 IG 等平台使用
- · 社群貼文與講座宣傳的視覺設計、Banner網頁廣告與展覽輸出物料製作
- 各種印刷物製作,包含海報、手冊、傳單和卡片等
- · 設計與公司企業視覺設計系統一致的PPT與Word等樣板檔案,提供50位同事使用

網頁設計

BFM 2019 - 2021

BFM 為廣告代理商,客戶多為國際品牌與食品大廠,亦代管經營電商網站。我的工作包括:

- 品牌官網與活動網站視覺設計,撰寫網站並解決各種跨平台問題
- · 使用內容管理系統 WordPress 設計製作網站
- · 設計印刷用的行銷宣傳物與商品,製作 Banner 與 Google GDN 動態 HTML 廣告
- · 剪輯與製作動態影像,產生吸睛與提高互動的 YouTube 與 Facebook 影片

美術指導

A Blissful Moment 2018 - 2019

- 產出視覺概念設計並審查外包美術品質,管理並協同創意團隊執行從概念發想直到專案完成
- 與概念設計、背景美術、動畫指導合作,確保導演的需求能在時間與預算內成功執行

概念設計

Gamania Digital Entertainment 2005 - 2017

在遊戲橘子內創意中心任職多年,專注於發展原創動畫電影與電視影集。工作包括:

- 擔任動畫前製美術視覺設計,並透過設計宣傳物、動態影像來行銷影集,協助《米各說》動畫賣到英國與日本,入園 10 多個國際影展。影集《水火 10 8》版權賣到全球 100 個國家
- 負責 FB 粉絲頁經營,3年內粉絲人數從0成長到35萬人
- 架設部門網站2年,管理後台主機並產出網站視覺與文字內容

美術編輯

XFUNS Creative Magazine 2003 - 2004

於放肆創意設計雜誌負責美術編輯與視覺設計